http://www.ombersleygolfclub.co.uk/terms-conditions/

HomeVisitor informationCovid-19 newsBook OnlineHow to book onlineGreen feesClub & buggy hireDriving range & practice areaCourse informationFor your safetySocietiesBar & restaurantSpecial occasionsSunday carveryBar menuReal aleMembershipMembership optionsWhy choose Ombersley?Frequently asked questionsCaptains & committeesCompetition resultsGolf academyLearn to play golfCourses & tuition feesJunior Golf AcademyLadies Golf CoachingGolf shopCustom golf clubsGolf club repairsBuying clubs online?News & eventsLatest newsEvents calendarContactHow to find usMeet the teamAbout usHow did we do?
Navigation
HomeVisitor information» Covid-19 news» Book Online» How to book online» Green fees» Club & buggy hire» Driving range & practice area» Course information» For your safetySocietiesBar & restaurant» Special occasions» Sunday carvery» Bar menu» Real aleMembership» Membership options» Why choose Ombersley?» Frequently asked questions» Captains & committees» Competition resultsGolf academy» Learn to play golf» Courses & tuition fees» Junior Golf Academy» Ladies Golf CoachingGolf shop» Custom golf clubs» Golf club repairs» Buying clubs online?News & events» Latest news» Events calendarContact» How to find us» Meet the team» About us» How did we do?
/
Terms and Conditions
Accessibility
The Ombersley Golf Club website has been built with the intention of making all content accessible to the widest range of visitors, regardless of technology, disability or impairment. We are continually working to increase the accessibility and usability of all areas of the site by adherence to recognised best practices and are working towards compliance with the W3C Web Content Accessibility Guidelines version 2.0.
In the meantime, should you experience any difficulty in accessing the Ombersley Golf Club website, please don't hesitate to contact us.
General disclaimer
Whilst every care has been taken in the preparation of the contents of this website, the security, fitness for purpose and the accuracy of such information is not implied and cannot be guaranteed. All information and materials on this website are for general information and do not constitute any advice or recommendation (professional or otherwise).
You should not rely upon any information on this website in making, or refraining from making, any specific decisions. Anyone, who uses information contained on this site, does so at their own risk and shall be deemed to have indemnified Ombersley Golf Club from any injuries or damages arising from such use.
We reserve the right to revise any dates, prices or information as a consequence of currency fluctuations, product price increases, product availability or other circumstances outside our control, and recommend that visitors contact Ombersley Golf Club for confirmation before taking any action based on the contents of this website.
Privacy policy (Reviewed in May 2018 for GDPR Regulations)
At Ombersley Golf Club we strive to protect your privacy and rights. We have set forth this statement to explain the information we collect from you, how we use that information, and your legal rights regarding that information.
Who has access to my information?
Any information you provide is controlled by John Dowty Ltd, Ombersley Golf Club, Bishops Wood Road, Ombersley, Droitwich, Worcestershire, WR9 0LE
("Data Controller").
What information do we collect and how do we use it?
When you choose to contact us through a web form, we may ask for your name, address, email address, and/or telephone number. This information will be used to send any information you request, or contact you if we need to respond to your question.
No cookies are used on this web site and no attempt is made to identify individual visitor through their IP address or ant other means. However, the following non-personal information may be collected for internal tracking to create summary statistics and to identify levels of interest in the information displayed on our site; Date and time of site access, IP address, web browser, operating system, screen resolution, search engine, search terms, domain and country.
How do we protect your information?
In accordance with UK Data Protection legislation we follow strict security procedures in the storage and disclosure of information you provide to prevent unauthorised access. Our procedures mean we may occasionally request proof of identity before disclosing information to you. We cannot however guarantee the security of any data you disclose to us online.
Do we disclose your information to third parties?
We do not sell, trade or rent your personal information to third parties for any reason whatsoever.
We occasionally employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. These may include packaging companies to fulfil orders, couriers to make deliveries and Royal Mail to send post. These companies may have access to your personal information, but may not use it for any other purpose and are required to process the data in accordance with UK data legislation.
Your consent and rights
By using our website you consent to the collection and use of this information by Ombersley Golf Club. Changes to this privacy policy will be posted to this page so that you are kept informed of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
Please note the information you provide will not be transferred out of the UK.
Under UK Data Protection legislation you have a right to see the personal information that we keep about you, upon receipt of written request (by post or email) to the address below.
Your comments
We welcome comments on our privacy policy. Please email your questions and comments to n.dowty@www.ombersleygolfclub.co.uk or call us on 01905 620747. Alternatively you can write to us at the following address:
The Data Controller, John Dowty Ltd, Ombersley Golf Club, Bishops Wood Road, Ombersley, Droitwich, Worcestershire, WR9 0LE
Newsletter and mailing list
In accordance with the 'The Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003' Ombersley Golf Club does not send unsolicited email, unless the recipient is an existing customer, or has given their permission to receive such material.
The sole purpose of our mailing list is to distribute occasional information regarding Ombersley Golf Club to those who have specifically requested it.
Should you wish to un-subscribe from our mailing list at any time, or you receive email from us in error, you will find details included in every email we send you. You will then receive one last email to confirm that your email address has been removed from our records.
If you have any further questions or suggestions, please email n.dowty@www.ombersleygolfclub.co.uk.
External links disclaimer
The links to third party external sites provided throughout this site are for the convenience of visitors only. These sites are maintained by other organisations and Ombersley Golf Club is not responsible for the content of these external sites and does not necessarily endorse the views or agree with the information held on these sites. In addition, we shall not be a party to, or in any way be responsible for, any transaction concerning goods or services available from such third party sites.
Copyright
All Web site design, text, graphics, the selection and arrangement thereof, the underlying source code and all other material on this Web site are copyright John Dowty Ltd, Ombersley Golf Club. All rights reserved. Registered Office Address: Bishops Wood Road, Ombersley, Droitwich, Worcestershire, WR9 0LE . Company Registration Number: 514940 Registered in England. VAT Registration Number: 274 7374 29.
Book a tee time
Contact us
How to Find Us
Reviews
Ombersley offers
New John Deere Mower
Return of competitive golf
Enjoy The Benefits of “Eating Out To Help Out” At Ombersley
To ensure your safety whilst visiting the bar and restaurant please help us by adhering to the following rules and procedures:
New John Deere Mower
Cleaning Of Range Balls
New John Deere mower
Ombersley Golf Club
Bishops Wood Road, Ombersley, Droitwich, Worcestershire, WR9 0LE
01905 620747
enquiries@ombersleygolfclub.co.uk
Terms & Conditions
